Daniel Precioso

daniprec.github.io | LinkedIn | GitHub | ResearchGate

Location: Madrid, Spain Email: <u>daniel.precioso@uca.es</u> ORCID: 0000-0003-3836-1429

DATA SCIENTIST

I am a highly skilled data scientist with over **5 years of experience** in **machine learning** and **Python**. With a passion for learning and growth, I am a highly motivated and proactive individual who enjoys working collaboratively to solve complex problems. My strong team work skills and ability to communicate effectively enable me to contribute to successful project outcomes.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : Python, Matlab, R

Libraries : NumPy, Pandas, scikit-learn, TensorFlow

Dev Tools : Visual Studio Code, Git, Github

Academic Tools: Latex

EXPERIENCE

Data ScientistSep 2022 – PresentKomorebi AIMadrid, Spain

- Data cleaning, manipulation and visualization.
- Design, train and deployment of machine learning and deep learning models with scikit-learn, including GB and CNN.
- Development of a dashboard to guide industrial decision making with Streamlit.

Predoctoral Research Staff

Sep 2019 – Aug 2022 *Cádiz, Spain*

University of Cádiz

- Collaboration with various industrial partners to conduct cutting-edge research in healthcare, energy and blue economy.
- Presentation of research findings to both technical and non-technical audiences.
- Publication of research papers in peer-reviewed journals.

Junior Data Scientist

Jan 2019 – Jun 2019

Fogum

Madrid, Spain

EDUCATION

Phd in Data Science University of Cádiz	Sep 2019 – Present <i>Cádiz, Spain</i>
MSc in Statistical and Computational Information Processing Universidad Politécnica de Madrid	Sep 2018 – Jul 2019 <i>Madrid, Spain</i>
Degree in Physics Complutense University of Madrid	Sep 2014 – Jul 2018 <i>Madrid, Spain</i>

PROJECTS

NeoCam *Machine Learning, Python* Reference!

•

CERTIFICATIONS

- Machine learning in Python with scikit-learn
- <u>TensorFlow in Practice Specialization</u>
- Applied Social Network Analysis in Python
- Applied Machine Learning in Python
- Applied Text Mining in Python
- Introduction to Data Science in Python

PUBLICATIONS

• <u>Neocam</u>